Last Call Pitches
Pitch Perfect 3 is a comedy, music film directed by Trish Sie.
After the highs of winning the world championships, the Bellas find themselves split apart
and discovering there aren't job prospects for making music with your mouth.
But when they get the chance to reunite for an overseas USO tour, this group of awesome nerds will
come together to make some music, and some questionable decisions, one last time.
Beca Mitchell, played by Anna Kendrick.
Patricia "Fat Amy" Hobart, played by Rebel Wilson.
Chloe Beale, played by Brittany Snow.
Emily Junk, played by Hailee Steinfeld.
Gail, played by Elizabeth Banks.
Aubrey Posen, played by Anna Camp.
Pitch Perfect 3 is a 2017 American musical comedy film directed by
Trish Sie and written by Kay Cannon and Mike White.
It is the sequel to Pitch Perfect 2 (2015), and the
final film in the Pitch Perfect trilogy.
The film features Anna Kendrick, Rebel Wilson, Hailee Steinfeld, Brittany Snow, Anna Camp, Hana Mae Lee, Ester Dean, Chrissie Fit, Alexis Knapp, Kelly Jakle, Shelley Regner,
John Michael Higgins, and Elizabeth Banks—all reprising their roles from previous films—as well as John Lithgow, DJ Khaled, Ruby Rose, Matt Lanter, and Guy Burnet.
The plot follows the a capella group the Bellas, who have graduated from college and
are reuniting for one final performance together as part of a USO tour.
Principal photography for Pitch Perfect 3 began in January
2017 in Atlanta, Georgia, and ended that April.
The film was released in the United States on December 22, 2017, and received mixed
reviews from critics, who deemed it inferior to its predecessors.
Nevertheless, it grossed $185 million worldwide against its $45 million budget.
It became the second-highest grossing musical comedy
film of all time, behind Pitch Perfect 2.
The film explores themes of sequel, singer, acapella, uso.
The tone is lighthearted.